<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Analysis Company</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Digital Analysis Company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Download original template</title>
      <link>/home/downloads/download1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/downloads/download1/</guid>
      <description>A simple, nice-looking call to action box. Boxing is about respect. getting it for yourself, and taking it away from the other guy. no, this is mount everest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Digital Analysis Company, your digital analytics partner. We specialize in data solutions to optimize your marketing, acquisition and product efforts.
We are a team of expert analysts and data scientists who are dedicated to your success. From comprehensive web and app analytics to insightful reporting, we work to craft powerful data strategies for your online growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Your privacy matters to us. Here&amp;rsquo;s how we handle your information:
Information Usage: We use your information solely to process your information requests.
Data Protection: We take measures to protect your data from unauthorized access.
Data Sharing: We never share your information without your consent.
Your Control: You can update or delete your info anytime by contacting us.
Policy Changes: We may update our policy; check back if needed.
Thanks for choosing us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Us We use Linkedin for first contact. Please reach out to us via our page for any inquiries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download HUGO template</title>
      <link>/home/downloads/download2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/downloads/download2/</guid>
      <description>Another simple, nice-looking call to action box. Boxing is about respect. getting it for yourself, and taking it away from the other guy. no, this is mount everest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GA4 Extract to AWS</title>
      <link>/home/recentworks/ga4_extract_to_aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/recentworks/ga4_extract_to_aws/</guid>
      <description>Send Daily GA4 Data to Amazon Via Big Query Summary Recently on a couple of occasions I have been asked to move GA4&amp;rsquo;s event data export into Amazon Web Services. Within GA4 you can configure an automatic export into a free Big Query sandbox. Data are retained for a rolling 60 days. Details. The export is only for Big Query.
You can export to a free instance of BigQuery (BigQuery sandbox), but exports that exceed the sandbox limits incur charges</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics &amp; GTM</title>
      <link>/home/services/google-analytics-tag-manager-meta-facebook-tiktok-pixel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/services/google-analytics-tag-manager-meta-facebook-tiktok-pixel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Optimize your site, app or campaign with informed decisions using data. Add GA4, Meta &amp;amp; TikTok tags using Google-Tag-Manager in a well well planned and thoroughly verified way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lifetime Value &amp; Retention</title>
      <link>/home/services/lifetime-value-ltv-churn-retention/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/services/lifetime-value-ltv-churn-retention/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The use of decay and growth functions enable businesses to maximize customer lifetime value, optimize profitability, and drive growth. Measure cohorts or users.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lifetime Value of Cohorts</title>
      <link>/home/recentworks/life_time_value_of_cohorts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/recentworks/life_time_value_of_cohorts/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning &amp; Stats Models</title>
      <link>/home/services/machine-learning-advanced-analytics-statistical-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/services/machine-learning-advanced-analytics-statistical-models/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Understand and explain the relationship between variables and outcomes, as well as effect sizes of incremental changes in input variables. Get directional and quantitative estimates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reporting &amp; Dashboards</title>
      <link>/home/services/reporting-dashboards-looker-tableau/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/services/reporting-dashboards-looker-tableau/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We provide you with easy-to-use dashboards that display all of your most important metrics in one place. Ad hoc analysis and business questions often end up as new dashboards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>subheader</title>
      <link>/home/subheader/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/subheader/</guid>
      <description>We specialize in providing data-driven insights to businesses, helping them make informed decisions to drive growth and achieve their goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Pixel Set Up</title>
      <link>/home/recentworks/tik_tok_pixel_setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/recentworks/tik_tok_pixel_setup/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
